Soumika has a string S and its starting index is 1.
The string S consists of characters from 1−9. As she is very intelligent, she wants to test his brother Vinay Tendulkar. 
She asked her brother Vinay Tendulkar to count the number of even numbered characters (2,4,6, 8)
For an index i, the result should be calculated from i to the end of the string. As Vinay doesn't know about programming, he wants you to help him find the solution.

Input - 
574674546476

Output - 
7 7 7 6 5 5 4 4 3 2 1 1
-----------------------------------------------------------------

Start from the right end of the string. Let f(i) denote the number of even characters from i till the end of the array.

f(length) = 0, if str[length] is odd
	  = 1, if str[length] is even, (We are starting from the end since we start from the rightmost end.)

For i = length to 1, do -
f(i) = f(i + 1),     if str[i] is odd
     = 1 + f(i + 1), if str[i] is even

Display f(i) for all i from 1 to length because they have asked for this value at every position.

If they had asked the number of even characters from beginning to end, it would be f(1).