You are given an array A1,A2...AN. You have to tell how many pairs (i, j) exist such that 1 ≤ i < j ≤ N and Ai XOR Aj is odd.

Input and Output 
First line T, the number of testcases. Each testcase: first line N, followed by N integers in next line. For each testcase, print the required answer in one line.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

(p, q) have an Odd XOR iff they have different parities. Since, we only count the pairs up to order, we allow p to take on all odd numbers, and q to take on even numbers.

The answer is (no_of_odd_numbers*no_of_even_numbers).