Dhoni has n days of vacations! So he decided to go either driving or do his cricket practice. Dhoni knows the following information about each of these n days:
 whether he can drive his car or not (due to odd-even rule) and whether the cricket academy is open for practice on that day. For the i-th day there are four options:

1.He can not drive his car and the academy is closed.

2.He can not drive his car and the academy is open.

3.He can drive his car and the academy is closed.

4.He can drive his car and the academy is open.

On each of these days Dhoni can either have rest or drive his car (if it is possible on this day), or go to academy (if the academy is open on this day).

Find the minimum number of days on which Dhoni will have rest (it means, he will not go driving and academy at the same time). The only limitation that Dhoni has — he does not want to do the same activity on two consecutive days: it means, he will not go for driving on two consecutive days, and academy for practice on two consecutive days.

Input Format

The first line contains a positive integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 100) — the number of days of Dhoni's holidays.

The second line contains the sequence of integers a1, a2, ..., an (0 ≤ ai ≤ 3) separated by space, where:

ai equals 0, if on the i-th day of holiday he can not drive his car and the academy is closed.

ai equals 1, if on the i-th day of holiday he can not drive his car and the academy is open.

ai equals 2, if on the i-th day of holiday he can drive his car and the academy is closed.

ai equals 3, if on the i-th day of holiday he can drive his car and the academy is open.

Output format

Print the minimum possible number of days on which Dhoni will have rest.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We need to keep track of two entities - activity possible on current day, activity performed on previous day.

if(current_activity = 0)
	Rest has to be taken
if(current_activity = previous_activity = 1 or 2),
	then that means he is forced to rest on the current day.
	Because only one activity is possible on the current day and it was already performed on the previous day. 
else
	if(current_activity = 3),
		then if previous day was 1, do 2 today,
		      if previous day was 2, do 1 today,
		     if previous day was 3 or 0, do 3 today. 

	else
		do whatever activity is scheduled. There is no conflict.

for i = 1 ... n
	if(current = 0) or (current_activity = previous_activity = 1 or 2),
		previous = 0, //Rest taken today 
		rest ++ 
	else
		if(current = 3)
			previous = (previous < 3) ? (3 - current) : current
		else
			previous = current //Do whatever was planned